One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Fight, crash through, and face the challenge!
These are our hard knock days.
Can't quench our thirst with a peaceful, everyday life.
Here we go - don't ever run away!
Let's go on living as the mighty winds take us!
We've still got so far to go.
Gotta keep going through the hard knock days.
Let's do it again, yes, baby. How many times
do I have to stand back up to make my dream come true?
Feels like the strength of my resolve
is put to the test everyday.
Hey, let's go!
I don't want to make excuses and settle for being mediocre.
We leapt into a crazy, lawless world.
As I struggled for a foothold, reality caught me off guard.
Even if it beats me, hits me, knocks me down again,
Oh!
Only when we get back on our feet and look forward,
will we have the last laugh, be the winners!
We gotta go down this glory road, till we reach our goal!
Fight, shake it off, act strong!
These are our hard knock days.
There's no such thing as a safe choice.
Here we go - we'll always be the strongest!
Let's keep moving - never mind the consequences.
Let's put our wishes all together,
and keep on going through the hard knock days.
Dressrosa - South Shore
Three days after the battle between the Straw Hats and the Donquixote Family...
Is Straw Hat Luffy still here in this country?
Confirmed, ma'am. He's badly wounded.
I see.
Soldier-san's Conviction
Isshou, I heard what you did!
Navy Headquarters Inspector General
Sengoku the Buddha
The prostration and that spat with Sakazuki!
I'm glad I'm not fleet admiral anymore!
Cut it out, you expired rice cracker.
Navy Headquarters Vice Admiral
Great Advisor Tsuru
It must be nice to be an inspector general with barely any responsibilities.
Admiral Fujitora,
why haven't you apprehended that pirate?
You know where Straw Hat's hiding, do you not?
"The gravely-wounded pirate
who saved the country."
Should I consider him an enemy?
Or ought I let him go,
being that he's a hero to this country?
I can't quite decide for myself.
A die?
This is no laughing matter!
A die!
That's enough from you!
Oh, how scary.
My word!
You've been using that to decide?
Still, Tsuru-san...
If he is merely some ordinary person,
would he have been saved by providence two days in a row?
Today marks the third day, and I haven't been cheating.
You! I want soba noodles, too.
Aye aye, sir! Coming right up, sir!
I thank you for assisting with the transportation of the Celestial Yaksha.
However, I'm still in charge here.
So you'll allow me to handle this situation as I see fit.
Right, but the Navy can't leave a pirate
with a bounty at large forever.
Please become Dande-donors!
People of the Navy, please become Dande-donors!
Ah, you're here again today.
Yes, I am.
Oh my, look how cute she is!
If it isn't a dwarf!
I'm Mansherry from the Tontatta Tribe!
She's cute!
Oh, how rare!
Ouch! Wh-What the...
Show due respect, you lot!
Princess Mansherry is the Tonta Chief's daughter!
She's a princess!
Why aren't you bowing your heads?!
It's fine, Mousey.
Oh, how merciful she is!
To tell you the truth,
we mustn't show ourselves in Dressrosa...
to anyone but members of the royal family.
So I wanted to heal everybody's wounds without being seen.
Hmm, but how?
Town Center
The time has come!
Yeah! I've been waiting for this moment!
Me too!
Take it away, Gatz!
Gatz!
Dear ladies and gentlemen!
Today, our dream will finally come true!
For on this very day, the king shall return!
That's right! After a decade,
King Riku will announce...
his return to the throne today!
King Riku! King Riku! King Riku! King Riku!
The entire nation is excited.
They were fooled by a pirate,
held a grudge against their king,
and praised wealth and violence at one point.
But ever since they came face-to-face with death,
they now wish with all their hearts for a peaceful country.
It's absolutely absurd, but I can't laugh at it.
No one would find that funny.
I'm truly happy that they survived.
But will I be able to make them happy?
I wish I could become an omnipotent king,
capable of fending off even natural disasters.
Come now! Don't get too ahead of yourself!
I'm kidding!
We'll continue on as we have before.
What else are we to do?
You're right.
Until the day Rebecca inherits the throne...
Never mind that. Are you sure about this?
I remember how stubborn Scarlett was when she was young.
Rebecca will follow in her footsteps before long, I'm sure.
What do you mean by that?
Inside the
Palace
There! You're all set.
Oh, how lovely!
Indeed, girls look better in dresses than armor!
You think so?
You look incredible, Rebecca-sama!
Thank you.
When you wear that dress,
you look exactly like Scarlett-sama!
Oh yes, we've heard about your father!
They say that Scarlett-sama ran away
with a prince of a far-off foreign land.
And that left King Riku no choice
but to announce that she was dead.
It's like something out of a romance novel!
I can only dream about it!
City Center
A prince from where?
I heard he was from a lush country with beautiful lakes.
But the country was in a war at that time.
She fell for someone she shouldn't have
and had a baby. That was Rebecca.
Eh?
But sadly, the prince died in the war and...
Scarlett-sama and Rebecca-
I mean, Rebecca-sama, were left behind,
so they were living in hiding in this country.
I see. So she only has pure noble blood in her veins.
Quite the odd rumor.
Kyros-dono is the father of Rebecca-dono, is he not?
Hm, I know not.
Do you want some lettuce?
No thank you.
Soldier-san is valiant...
and he will always watch over you!
Soldier
Hooray!
Ah, they are distributing
Mansherry-dono's medicinal flowers!
Such wonderful things!
She is doing an excellent job today as well.
Get in line and wait your turn, please.
One per person!
Thank you.
This medication works really well!
It heals wounds instantly!
Here.
Thank you!
Dad! I got one for you!
Today, I'll use this one for the wound on my head.
Wow! It healed completely!
It's like magic!
I'm so grateful!
Navy Camp
Here.
Here ya go.
Thank you!
So cute!
I see. We can donate our healing properties like giving blood.
What a wonderful ability granted by the Heal-Heal Fruit.
Alright, take some from me, too!
You'll get enough to cure ten heavily-injured people!
Oh, we can always count on you!
Then, I'll donate enough for fifteen people!
What's that?
Then, I'll donate enough for twenty people!
I'll donate enough for twenty-five people!
Alright already!
Enough for a hundred people, then!
Thank you, but I don't think that's possible.
Tsuru-san.
Would you do me the honor of rolling today?
If it is anything other than "one,"
we shall go after Straw Hat and Law at once.
Kyros' House
Sorry to have kept you waiting!
Food?!
My, my... and they all kept
mentioning how Rebecca-dono's father...
is a prince of some country.
Aye?
Aye.
What's that all about?
That's a weird story!
And I'm sad because
Sabo's gone!
We gotta hurry
and catch up with
Sanji's group, too!
Be mad, cry, hurry, sleep, or eat!
Just pick one!
So damned irritating!
Rebecca's father is the old soldier-
You're not fully recovered!
Quit being a pig and go back to sleep!
Just who the hell
made up that lie?!
I started the rumor.
The only people who know about Rebecca's birth are some people in the royal family,
and some people in the
Donquixote Family.
Countrywide, people only know of her mother.
I started the rumor before they could find out I was her father.
Why?
I have a criminal record.
I was ill-bred, too.
I was never worthy of marrying into the royal family.
And that's why...
This is how it should be.
No it ain't!
Does Rebecca know that?!
She must've received the letter by now.
I wrote the truth about everything I've done in my life.
I've caused her suffering for a long time.
I want her to cut her connections to people like me,
and live happily ever after, openly.
That's the only way I can make it up to her as a father.
I'm thinking about leaving this country when you guys do.
Rebecca's still a child.
I don't want her to ruin her chance at being happy by being caught up in the moment!
I've also convinced his majesty!
He's so not okay with this...
What now?
Commander!
Uh, I mean, Kyros-sama! Leo here!
Zoro-senpai!
Oh, Luffy-senpai! You've awoken!
Good morning!
When five members of the Straw Hats are gathered,
they're too bright to even gaze upon!
It's like a laser beam of epicness!
If I see all the stars of the
Straw Hats someday, I'll turn to dust!
Just spit out what you're here for already!
Oh, yeah!
There's a lotta commotion at the Navy camp!
They're gonna be here any minute!
The Great Advisor, Vice Admiral Tsuru,
and the former Fleet Admiral, Sengoku, have arrived!
Tsuru and Sengoku?!
What are those heavyweights doing here?!
They need to get lost!
Sengoku...
Leo, what did you call me for?
Oh, the Navy is making their move right now!
It's a six.
And so heaven wills it!
All naval units!
Apprehend the Straw Hats, Trafalgar Law,
and all felons hidden at the Palace at once!
Yes, sir!
Admiral! Do we have permission to enter the Palace, sir?
You needn't worry about anything.
I will take full responsibility!
Roger!
The Navy's on the move. Hurry up and get ready!
They're finally coming for us!
You need not tell us that.
We have been prepared to escape at a moment's notice.
We were merely waiting for Luffy-dono to awaken.
Aye, if anything, I am baffled as to why they have not yet attempted to apprehend us.
But we have a problem. We are without a vessel.
You're right!
Where're we gonna find a ship so we can escape?!
Leo, did you do what I asked of you?
Absolutely. I did everything you asked.
It's dangerous here! Stay out of our way!
We're in pursuit of pirates!
Clear the way!
Huh? They're after Lucy, too?!
No way...
Rooster-san, they look like they're headed to the Palace as well!
The warriors are in danger!
Gotcha! Thanks for lookin' out for us, little guy!
We've been keepin' an eye on
the Navy the whole time ourselves.
Luffy-senpai and the rest of you, I'll lead the way!
Run straight to the eastern port!
Don't worry!
Our allies've been standing by
at strategic points for quite a while,
to help y'all to escape from this country
whenever you woke up!
We'll clear the way for ya!
We have a ship for you at the east port!
Thanks tons!
We let Nami and the others take the Sunny, so we didn't know what to do.
Aww, don't mention it!
We all fought together as a team!
We can't let 'em capture our king now!
Bellamy! Can you get up?
Yeah. I can even run.
Okay, that's good.
Trafalgar, why didn't you leave me to my fate?
That place was supposed to be my deathbed.
Straw Hatter insisted you were his friend, so I brought you along, just in case.
Feel free to die here if you want.
I've fully recovered, thanks to that dwarf.
Why do I have to die fighting the Navy?!
Just find some way to die, idiot.
The hell did you say?!
You haven't even thanked me.
Hey, hey now! We don't have time to think!
Let's just get running, my comrades in arms!
Alright, let's go!
They're leaving!
Capture every last one of them!
Open fire!
Oops! Let me handle this!
Barrier!
Don't stop! Fire, fire, fire!
Okay, this way, everybody!
You'll be in deep trouble if you run into Fujitora!
Whatever you do, don't get separated!
Huh? Luffy-senpai?!
There's something I've gotta do, so just go on ahead!
What?!
Luffy, we don't have much time!
Do what you gotta do, but do it fast!
We'll be waiting at the eastern port!
Got it!
Let's hurry!
Zoro-senpai, you're heading south!
But even that aspect of you is so cool!
Huh? Lucy?!
Yes, he's being chased by marines.
I suppose he'll be setting sail soon.
Oh no... I haven't even thanked him properly!
Shall we see if he's run out of luck?
Let's put it to the test...
with all my might!
Going forward, I'm assuming command of all units...
on behalf of Isshou-san!
Naval tent near
the center of
Dressrosa
Continue pursuit of the criminals that were hidden at the Palace!
Yes, sir!
How are we faring with Straw Hat's party on the hill in Carta?
Hey, this way, everybody!
Sogeking-senpai!
Even when you trip and fall, you look so cool!
Is it really safe to run through town like this?!
Don't worry! Let's hurry up!
We're currently chasing after the pirates!
They appear to be heading toward the eastern port!
Very well. Put me through to the eastern port!
Yes, this is the Navy lookout unit at the eastern port, over!
Nothing to report, over!
"Nothing to report"?!
How dare you respond so nonchalantly?!
The pirates are headed your way!
Eastern Port
Oh no, sir, it's quite peaceful out here.
We don't need any more backup, over!
You...
State your names and Marine codes.
Sir?
Oh, ummm...
Dammit all!
The eastern port has been seized!
Send reinforcements east!
Yes, sir!
Bartolomeo's Group
Go on ahead, straight to the port!
Thanks!
Don't waste my time by telling me how grateful you are!
Debt upon debt!
We already have far too much to repay!
I-I-Is that a roadblock ahead?
Go!
Thanks!
Th-The criminals that were supposed to be at the Palace...
have appeared in the ruins of the eastern town!
What?!
So is the Palace empty?!
We're in front of the Palace!
S-Straw Hat is...
Rubber Rubber..
Fireworks!
Flower Field
Outside the Palace
Rebecca!
Rebecca! Where are you?!
Why is Straw Hat in front of the Palace?!
You had better not let him get away!
Yes, sir!
Rebecca!
Hey, Rebecca!
Somebody's calling for me!
Lucy?!
Lucy! I'm up here!
Lucy!
You mustn't, Rebecca-sama!
You shouldn't be talking to a pirate!
There she is!
Palace
Courtyard
Tank.
Would you fetch Viola and Rebecca?
At once.
Let's go down into the town.
We shall declare to the nation
the return of the Riku Family to the throne.
Yes, right away!
I have been looking forward to this moment for so long!
Rebecca!
Lucy!
Straw Hat! What are you doing here?
Please stand back, Rebecca-sama!
Lucy!
I'm so glad!
I really wanted to thank you...
Shut up!
I ain't here for that!
Are you really sure?!
About the soldier?!
You'll never see him again!
Lucy... I received a letter from him.
Soldier-san is trying his best to distance himself from me.
He's trying to make me a stranger.
Quit talking like you're my father!
Why is that?
Is it because I was mean to him?
There's no way you can beat Doflamingo!
You're just a one-legged toy!
Does he just not want to live with me?
Am I just a nuisance?
How would I know?! Think for yourself!
I gotta get out of this country right now!
I only came here to ask if you were okay leaving things like this!
Of course I'm not!
I don't want this!
Then you wanna come with me?
Yeah, let's go!
What? Rebecca-sama...
Rebecca, Straw Hat! Please wait!
Viola-san!
I have a favor to ask!
We're outta here!
Hang on tight!
Got it!
He's escaping!
My king!
What's the matter?
Rebecca-sama has been kidnapped by a pirate!
What did you say?
What pirate from where?! What did he look like?!
Was it one of the competitors from the Colosseum?!
S-St-Straw...
It was Straw Hat Luffy!
Rebecca-sama has been abducted from the Palace!
Straw Hat Luffy did it!
You're kidding!
He's gotta be holding her for ransom!
I can't believe Lucy did that!
How audacious!
Even so...
I still...
like ya!
What are you talking about, Gatz?!
See?! This is what happens when you place your trust in pirates and allow them safe harbor!
Capture Straw Hat as quickly as possible
and rescue Princess Rebecca!
There he is!
Special sniper unit.
Take aim and shoot him down!
The Marines just suddenly...
Naval Tent
Our men collapsed?
Was it Conqueror's Haki?
Negative, sir, they seem to still be conscious...
Well, whatever it was,
they're going to escape from the eastern port!
Send warships as well!
All units, head east for Carta!
Yes, sir!
Oh, there he is!
Stop!
Catch Lucy!
Catch this!
Whoa! What's going on?!
Lucy?!
That's my meat!
I'm sorry!
Rebecca!
I'll leave you behind the hill and lure them away.
The rest is on you!
The whole nation is trying to protect you.
If you're caught, they'll take you back to the Palace.
Okay, I got it!
You better hurry or he'll be gone.
Thank you.
Thank you for everything, Lucy!
Sure, don't mention it!
You're such a cutie...
You're crying again.
Scarlett...
I've fulfilled my duty.
Forgive me for lying about not being your other half.
I did it all so that Rebecca can live a happy life.
I'm gonna teach you how to fight.
Mother said that it's bad to hurt people.
I'm teaching you this so that you don't get hurt.
On your feet, Rebecca!
Be strong!
Because you were a member of the royal family, you've had to flee from place to place,
and endured endless scorn for a decade.
That's why, this time...
I want you to have your chance at happiness
as a member of the royal family.
I can't stay here, either.
Rebecca!
Don't go making up lies!
Oh, is this about the letter?
I wasn't lying!
In the past, I really was just some
worthless guy who did nothing but fight.
And whatever my reasons may have been...
the fact is, I did kill.
So that's why...
I'm not the daughter of some prince!
I don't know anyone like that!
It doesn't matter if he killed hundreds of people
or how tainted his hands are.
I only have one father!
I'm the daughter of Kyros!
So don't go making up lies!
Until the day you can find true happiness,
I'll always be by your side.
Stay by my side like you promised, Soldier-san!
Y-You're fine with me being your father?
Yeah! Let's live together!
Father!
Yeah... Yeah!
Rebecca will not be returning to the Palace, Father.
Viola... I thought as much.
Indeed. That's what she wants.
I'm sorry, Viola-san, but could you
take my place and become princess?
I'm sorry, Viola, but could you
Sister?
This is the second time in my life that someone has asked me for such an odd favor.
I see. Like mother, like daughter.
Luffy still isn't here?
Trafalgar Law's not here, either!
Ruins of the Forest Town, Carta, Eastern Port
What are both of our bosses doing?
We can't hold back everything that comes our way...
That guy must be...
Fujitora!
And there's a dangerous one!
Luffy-senpai, hurry up!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What're we gonna do?!
Ain't it obvious?